{
    "id": "bfdee9917dda48f19d7428e07337e69f",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He accumulated a fortune buying and selling used cars. Identify the noun.",
            "description": "A noun refers to a person, place, thing or idea. ",
            "answers": [
                "accumulated",
                "fortune",
                "selling"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The drawing of the house is accurate in every detail. Identify the adjective.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drawing",
                "house",
                "accurate"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has acquired a working knowledge of French. Identify the verb.",
            "description": "Working is a present participle. Present participles are not verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "acquired",
                "working",
                "knowledge"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was criticized for one careless act. Identify the adjective.",
            "description": "Careless modifies the noun act.",
            "answers": [
                "criticized",
                "careless",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Act now and save money during our annual sale. Identify the conjunction.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "now",
                "and",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an acquisitive person, always wanting things. Identify the adverb.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acquisitive",
                "always",
                "wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A gentleman must conduct himself well in any situation. Identify the pronoun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gentleman",
                "conduct",
                "himself"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Addition is taught before subtraction. Identify the preposition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "addition",
                "taught",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The chameleon adapts to the surroundings by changing color. Identify the verb.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adapts",
                "surroundings",
                "changing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Letâ€™s add up the cost of all our purchases. Identify the preposition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "add",
                "up",
                "our"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "All nations must work for the accomplishment of peace. Identify the adjective.",
            "description": "All modifies the noun nations.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "accomplishment",
                "peace"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am an adult and I expect to be treated accordingly. Identify the adverb.",
            "description": "Most words ending in ly are adverbs. Adverbs modify verbs, adjectives or other adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "adult",
                "treated",
                "accordingly"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}